Sundays at Tiffany's is a drama, romance, tv movie
film directed by Mark Piznarski.
Jane, a soon-to-be-married woman, is reunited with her
imaginary friend Michael who returns in a human form.
Soon, Jane begins doubting her feelings for her
fiance as she gets attracted to Michael.
Jane Claremont, played by Alyssa Milano.
Michael Friend, played by Eric Winter.
Jacqueline, played by Kristin Booth.
Young Jane, played by Emily Alyn Lind.
Hugh Morrison, played by Ivan Sergei.
Vivian Claremont, played by Stockard Channing.
Sundays at Tiffany's is a 2008 romance novel by James
Patterson and Gabrielle Charbonnet.
It was adapted into a Lifetime Television original movie that premiered in 2010.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, imaginary friend,
true love, mother daughter relationship, dominant mother.
The tone is emotional.